<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Techsnapie Magazines</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com</link>
	<description>Technical news updates at your fingertips</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 02:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Untitled-design-1-modified-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Techsnapie Magazines</title>
	<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">198140128</site>	<item>
		<title>Future of agriculture in India &#8211; Digital agriculture</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/future-of-agriculture-in-india-digital-agriculture/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/future-of-agriculture-in-india-digital-agriculture/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harshini]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 02:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agriculture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digitalworld]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ML]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=2002</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technical interventions based on remote sensing, soil sensors, unmanned aerial surveys, and market data are used in digital agriculture to allow farmers to combine crop and soil health conditions at &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/future-of-agriculture-in-india-digital-agriculture/">Future of agriculture in India &#8211; Digital agriculture</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Technical interventions based on remote sensing, soil sensors, unmanned aerial surveys, and market data are used in digital agriculture to allow farmers to combine crop and soil health conditions at various stages of production, allowing for imagining and testing. They can be used as a starting point for recognising possible problems and equipping employees with the tools they need to address them quickly.</p>



<p>Artificial Intelligence / Machine Learning (AL/ML) algorithms that boost crop yields, eliminate pests, assist in soil testing, provide useful data to farmers, and minimise their burden can produce actionable insights in a short amount of time. Farm manipulation, inventories, rapid and secure transactions, and food tracking are all possible with blockchain technology.</p>



<p>Farmers would no longer have to rely on papers or files to record and keep critical information. Robots, temperature and humidity sensors, aerial images, and GPS technology are some of the technologies that will be employed in future agriculture. Modern agricultural and robotic technologies will be able to make farms more profitable, efficient, safe, and ecologically friendly as a result of this. Governments can play a key role in resolving the issue of food scarcity. They need to take on a bigger and more important role than just regulating and facilitating. </p>



<p>Governments can challenge the traditional heritage paradigm and advance such projects by challenging the traditional heritage model;</p>



<ul><li>To begin, ensure food security and reduce import dependency.</li><li>Become a net exporter of new solutions as well as products.</li><li>Boost productivity and aid in the transition to a knowledge-based economy.</li></ul>



<h3 id="implementation-of-digital-agriculture-in-india">Implementation of digital agriculture in India</h3>



<p>The importance of isolated smallholder farms in India, which complicates data collecting, is one of the driving forces behind the country&#8217;s progressive adoption of digital farming. Limited access to machinery, as well as periodic natural calamities like as droughts, floods, and excessive monsoon rains, have slowed the adoption of digital solutions in the sector. As a result, establishing digital agriculture on a typical Indian small farm will require a customised method, which can later be enlarged and made available to a large number of Indian farms.</p>



<ul><li>Low-cost technology</li><li>Portable hardware</li><li>Academic support</li></ul>



<h3 id="benefits">Benefits</h3>



<ul><li>Agriculture production is increased while costs are reduced.</li><li>Prevents soil degradation</li><li>Reduces the usage of chemical fertilizers in crop production.</li><li>Encourages the effective and efficient use of water resources.</li><li>Reduces the influence on the environment</li><li>Increase worker safety.</li></ul>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/future-of-agriculture-in-india-digital-agriculture/">Future of agriculture in India &#8211; Digital agriculture</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/future-of-agriculture-in-india-digital-agriculture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2002</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Badaga tradition</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/badaga-tradition/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/badaga-tradition/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Abitha Bojraj]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga festivals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga occupation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga tradition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[badaga traditional dress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1820</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Badagars have their unique language called &#8221; badugu” and it is  not the dialect of any language which was proved by a French linguist Christin Pilot Raichoor on her research. &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/badaga-tradition/">Badaga tradition</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Badagars have their unique language called &#8221; badugu” and it is  not the dialect of any language which was proved by a French linguist Christin Pilot Raichoor on her research. Badaga language don’t have a keen written scripts Badagas are the aboriginal tribes of Nilgiris.Most of the badagas live in the  Nilgiri district.There are around 400 villages in Nilgiris whereas it is only been spoken yet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img src="https://www.clubmahindra.com/blog/media/section_images/untitled-2-eaee0c4ebc066f3.jpg" alt="ooty" width="1000" height="500" /></figure>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="history"><strong>History</strong></h3>



<p>It is said that badagas have been migrated from southern mysore provinces ,mainly from Nanjangud and Ummatur.Later the Ummatur Rayas ‘ empire declined and it led to the fall in the customs and traditions of the badagas.</p>



<p>Nilgiris was called as badaga nad or badaga country by Frederic prince,1908:15,16”,”W.Francis,1908:209”,R.Sugumaran,2014:13”.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="culture"><strong>Cultu</strong>re</h3>



<p>Badaga cultures were&nbsp; very rich and unique.Badagars celebrate each and every ceremony such as naming ceremony,where a child receives its name on seventh ,ninth or eleventh day,puberty ceremony in which the girl is given a ceremonial wash and decorated with dresses and ornaments ,and a marriage ceremony where dowry is unthinkable among badagas.”thaali “ a rope is tied by the male is a special indentification for the outsiders to know that the girl is married,and the last is the death ceremony ,when the person dies , a gold coin called” sinnatha hana “is placed in their mouth.Death ceremony in badagas are more complicated.When &nbsp;death occurs the respective villagers should take the responsibility while the family doesn’t have any burden. </p>



<h4 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="traditional-dress"><strong>Traditional Dress</strong></h4>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The tribal costume of the badaga men consist of white turban ,a long cloth with red,black and gold stripes which is wrapped round through one end is over his shoulder called” seelae “and a white cloth tied over the head called “ mandarae”.</p>



<p>                 Woman wear a white cloth covering body called  &#8220;mundu&#8221; and  &#8220;thundu” which is tied around her chest.and a cloth tied around head called “pattu”.</p>



<h4 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="festivals"><strong>Festivals</strong></h4>



<p>                    Badagas called festivals as” HABBA” .They are mainly hethai and ayya deties.The celebration of hethai habba is spread over the month of DecemberJanuary over all villages.All are used to wear white and white in this festival.people from outside are provided food all the time of the festival days specially called as &#8220;annadhana”.</p>



<h4 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="occupation"><strong>Occupation</strong></h4>



<p>     Primary occupation of the badagas is agriculture.Many work on tea and coffee estates and some tend a flock of sheep,and some with the buffalos and cows.</p>



<h4 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="food"><strong>Food</strong></h4>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Most of the ancestors ate hatchikae which was made using little millet or samai which is suited for all age groups.and some grains are roasted in earthen pot called madakae with a hole on the side using a wooden stick with a cloth tied at the end and another special food called eragi ittu which is done using finger millets which are the alternatives of rice and wheat which is eaten up with ghee, greens and beans curry called avarae udhakka in badaga are the some of the best and famous food of badaga culture.</p>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In a while the dish ganjikae that is barely have also became a rarity.</p>



<p>Ancestors of badagas made sure that they prepare almost everything from scratch butter ,curd ,ghee all were prepared from milk of cows or buffalos of their own and that was the great period of badaga culture with  the heathy food and healthy life. Now the increase in the cultivation of tea led to the decline in the cultivation of millets and other grains in Nilgiris.</p>



<p>They firmly believe that if more people followed older tradition ,both the people and earth would be healthier.</p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/badaga-tradition/">Badaga tradition</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/badaga-tradition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1820</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Check Out the different types of Pen Testing</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-different-types-of-pen-testing/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-different-types-of-pen-testing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yogesh K B]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[cyber Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybercrime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybersecurity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pen testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[penetration testing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While it&#8217;s tempting to just request that a tester &#8220;test everything,&#8221; this would most likely lead to pen testers only scratching the surface of several vulnerabilities, sacrificing gathering valuable intelligence &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-different-types-of-pen-testing/">Check Out the different types of Pen Testing</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>While it&#8217;s tempting to just request that a tester &#8220;test everything,&#8221; this would most likely lead to pen testers only scratching the surface of several vulnerabilities, sacrificing gathering valuable intelligence gained by going more in-depth in fewer areas, with clear objectives in mind.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://techgenix.com/tgwordpress/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/Penetration-testing-Shutterstock.jpg" alt="pen test
"/></figure>



<p>To make sure pen tests can achieve these objectives and pinpoint weaknesses, various different types of pen tests focus on different areas of an IT infrastructure, including:<br>&nbsp;</p>



<h3 id="web-application-tests"><strong><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Web Application Tests</mark></strong></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://usersnap.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/web-application-testing.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Web application penetration tests examine the overall security and potential risks of web applications, including coding errors, broken authentication or authorization, and injection vulnerabilities.</p>



<h3 id="network-security-tests"><strong><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Network Security Tests</mark></strong></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://content.secureworks.com/-/media/Images/Insights/2020/abstract-0042_blue-fly-in/blue-fly-in_1600x650.ashx?modified=20200805145848" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Network penetration testing aims to prevent malicious acts by finding weaknesses before the attackers do. Pen testers focus on&nbsp;network security testing&nbsp;by exploiting and uncovering vulnerabilities on different types of networks, associated devices like routers and switches, and network hosts. They aim to exploit flaws in these areas, like weak passwords or misconfigured assets, to gain access to critical systems or data.</p>



<h3 id="cloud-security-tests"><strong><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Cloud Security Tests</mark></strong></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.coalfire.com/medialib/assets/images/Resources-New/Webinars/Hacking-Cloud_814px2.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Security teams to work with cloud providers and third-party vendors to design and carry out cloud security testing for cloud-based systems and applications. Cloud pen-testing validates the security of a cloud deployment, identifies overall risk and likelihood for each vulnerability, and recommends how to improve your cloud environment.</p>



<h3 id="iot-security-tests"><strong><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">IoT Security Tests</mark></strong></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="http://read.nxtbook.com/wiley/plasticsengineering/october2016/coverstory/earth.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Pen testers take the nuances of different IoT devices into account by analyzing each component and the interaction between them. By using the layered methodology, where each layer is analyzed, pen testers can spot weaknesses that may otherwise go unnoticed.</p>



<h3 id="social-engineering"><strong><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Social Engineering</mark></strong></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://cdn.builtin.com/sites/www.builtin.com/files/styles/ckeditor_optimize/public/inline-images/national/other-penetration-testing-certification.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Social engineering is a breach tactic, which involves using deception to gain access or information that will be used for malicious purposes. The most common example of this is seen in phishing scams. Pen testers use phishing tools and emails tailored to an organization to test defence mechanisms, detection and reaction capabilities, finding susceptible employees and security measures that need improvement.</p>



<h3 id="conclusion"><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Conclusion</mark></h3>



<p>Penetration testing can help to mitigate the threats of the above risks that your business may face. However, good security practices should be adopted in order to secure your business.</p>



<p><strong>Reference </strong>:</p>



<p><a href="https://www.coresecurity.com/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.coresecurity.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">https://www.coresecurity.com/</a></p>



<p><strong>check out the last blog:</strong></p>



<p><a href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/</a></p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-different-types-of-pen-testing/">Check Out the different types of Pen Testing</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-different-types-of-pen-testing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1982</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top World Heritage Sites and Indian Cultural Heritage</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-world-heritage-sites-and-indian-cultural-heritage/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-world-heritage-sites-and-indian-cultural-heritage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sangavi kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 01:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[indian cultural heritage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top world heritage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world heritage sites]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>1. Sun Temple&#160;&#160; &#160;Here’s the key bit of information about the Konark Sun Temple which is a UNESCO World Heritage site. The Konark or&#160;Konarak Sun temple&#160;is dedicated to the&#160;Hindu&#160;sun god&#160;Surya, &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-world-heritage-sites-and-indian-cultural-heritage/">Top World Heritage Sites and Indian Cultural Heritage</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="1-sun-temple">1. Sun Temple&nbsp;&nbsp;</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://media.istockphoto.com/photos/konark-sun-temple-orissa-india-picture-id1153631064?b=1&amp;k=20&amp;m=1153631064&amp;s=170667a&amp;w=0&amp;h=G_aHoSC9pU_9nw-VT7kVTCJPVBgjJG5tuNLzCObZoBs=" alt="World heritage sites" width="500" height="400"/><figcaption>                                     </figcaption></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;Here’s the key bit of information about the Konark Sun Temple which is a UNESCO World Heritage site. The Konark or&nbsp;Konarak Sun temple&nbsp;is dedicated to the&nbsp;Hindu&nbsp;sun god&nbsp;Surya, and, conceived as a giant stone&nbsp;chariot&nbsp;with 12 wheels, it is the most famous of the few sun temples built in&nbsp;India. It is located about 35 km northeast of the&nbsp;city&nbsp;of Puri on the coastline in the state of Odisha (earlier Orissa). Konark is a coastal town which means that the best time to visit it during the winters.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="2-ajanta-caves">  2. Ajanta Caves</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.tripsavvy.com/thmb/-aMTWDB0eYHS9Hzbvb_oeGEtBk0=/2121x1414/filters:no_upscale():max_bytes(150000):strip_icc()/GettyImages-469869640-6c29b1f8f7554daa9094d6b5f39a839a.jpg" alt="" width="500" height="400"/></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Ajanta Caves, Buddhist rock-cut&nbsp;cave&nbsp;temples and monasteries, located near Ajanta village, north-central&nbsp;Maharashtra&nbsp;state, western&nbsp;India, that are celebrated for their wall paintings.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="3-ellora-caves">3. Ellora Caves</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://media.istockphoto.com/photos/ellora-caves-buddhist-temples-in-arrangabad-india-picture-id483561330?b=1&amp;k=20&amp;m=483561330&amp;s=170667a&amp;w=0&amp;h=avvRa0GcnQkAcwv2PHAp-vBeYtAuQ3Sdf2U_M6lAlpQ=" alt="Ellora" width="500" height="400"/></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;Ellora Caves,&nbsp; a series of 34 magnificent rock-cut temples in northwest-central&nbsp;Maharashtra&nbsp;state, western&nbsp;India. They are located near the village of Ellora, 19 miles (30 km) northwest of&nbsp;Aurangabad&nbsp;and 50 miles (80 km) southwest of the&nbsp;Ajanta Caves.</p>



<p>Ellora served as a group of monasteries (viharas) and temples (caityas); some of the caves include sleeping cells that were carved for itinerant monks.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="4-nanda-devi-valley-of-flowers-national-park">4. Nanda Devi &amp; Valley of Flowers National Park</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.rvatemples.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Nanda-Devi-Temple.jpg?fit=1024%2C683&amp;ssl=1" alt="nanda devi" width="500" height="400"/></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;Nestled high in West Himalaya, India’s Valley of Flowers National Park is renowned for its meadows of endemic alpine flowers and outstanding natural beauty. This richly diverse area is also home to rare and endangered animals</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="5-khajuraho-group-of-monument">5. Khajuraho Group of Monument</h3>



<p>&nbsp;Located in Chattarpur district of Madhya Pradesh, Khajuraho is the pride of Indian architectural grandeur. Khajuraho attracts attention not for its presiding deities or religious importance, but rather for the incredible carvings and designs depicted on the temple walls.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="6-taj-mahal">6. Taj Mahal</h3>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1565505204576-1cc4b41662eb?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjEyMDd9&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=1000&amp;q=80" alt="Taj mahal" width="500" height="400"/></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Taj Mahal is a mausoleum complex in&nbsp;Agra, western Uttar Pradesh state, northern India. The Taj Mahal is also one of the world&#8217;s most iconic monuments, visited by millions of tourists each year. Every year tourists&nbsp;amounting to twice the total population of Agra visit&nbsp;the city for spotting Taj Mahal. To immortalize his love for his favorite wife, Mumtaz Mahal, the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan built the most amazing mausoleum of all times. The main expression of this building is pure love.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="7-hill-forts-of-rajasthan">7. Hill forts of Rajasthan</h3>



<p>The North Western Indian State of&nbsp;Rajasthan&nbsp;has over one hundred fortifications on hills and mountainous terrain. Six&nbsp;Hill Forts of Rajasthan, spread across&nbsp;Rajasthan&nbsp;state in northern&nbsp;India, have been clustered as a series and designated&nbsp;UNESCO World Heritage Site. The serial site, situated in the state of Rajastahan, includes six majestic forts in&nbsp;Chittorgarh; Kumbhalgarh; Sawai Madhopur; Jhalawar; Jaipur, and Jaisalmer.</p>



<p>They consist of:</p>



<ol type="1"><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chittor_Fort" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Chittor Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Chittorgarh</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kumbhalgarh" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Kumbhalgarh Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Kumbhalgarh</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ranthambore_Fort" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Ranthambore Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Sawai Madhopur</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gagron_Fort" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Gagron Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Jhalawar</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amber_Fort" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Amer Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Jaipur</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jaisalmer_Fort" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Jaisalmer Fort</a>&nbsp;at&nbsp;Jaisalmer</li></ol>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="8-mountain-railways-of-india">8. Mountain railways of India</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://lp-cms-production.imgix.net/features/2018/06/GettyImages-183471749-ca4e9c2903b2.jpg?auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;sharp=10&amp;vib=20&amp;ixlib=react-8.6.4&amp;w=850" alt="" width="500" height="400"/></figure></div>



<p>India’s three most visited scenic hill stations that attract both adventurers and leisure escapers are Darjeeling in north of West Bengal, Shimla in Himachal Pradesh and Ooty in Tamil Nadu. Although these hill stations can be easily accessed by road, yet the launch of mountain railways in India. the Darjeeling Himalayan Railway, Kalka-Shimla Railway and Nilgiri Mountain Railway started gaining in importance and were together declared as&nbsp;UNESCO World Heritage Site.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="9-rock-shelters-of-bhimbetka">9. Rock shelters of Bhimbetka</h3>



<p>The&nbsp;Bhimbetka Rock Shelter&nbsp;has the oldest-known rock art in India, as well as is one of the largest prehistoric complexes to be seen.&nbsp;</p>



<p>An archaeological treasure, Bhimbetka has around 243 rock shelters and have earned the honour of&nbsp;UNESCO World Heritage Site. The paintings found in the rock shelters here have a striking resemblance to the ones discovered in Kakadu National Park in Australia; to the cave paintings of Bushmen in Kalahari Desert and Upper Palaeolithic Lascaux cave paintings in France.</p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-world-heritage-sites-and-indian-cultural-heritage/">Top World Heritage Sites and Indian Cultural Heritage</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-world-heritage-sites-and-indian-cultural-heritage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1755</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan becomes world&#8217;s first bank in the metaverse</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/jpmorgan-becomes-worlds-first-bank-in-the-metaverse/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/jpmorgan-becomes-worlds-first-bank-in-the-metaverse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kavya suresh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1857</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>JPMorgan has become world’s first bank to enter a completely virtual world of the metaverse. Within Decentraland, users can buy virtual plots of land in the form of NFTs and &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/jpmorgan-becomes-worlds-first-bank-in-the-metaverse/">JPMorgan becomes world&#8217;s first bank in the metaverse</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>JPMorgan has become world’s first bank to enter a completely virtual world of the metaverse.</p>



<p>Within Decentraland, users can buy virtual plots of land in the form of NFTs and make purchases using cryptocurrency backed by the Ethereum blockchain.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.9jafinder.ng/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/20220216_092039-1024x834.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Users have described their experience in the Onyx lounge on Twitter, noting the picture of CEO Jamie Dimon and a tiger lurking around. On top of that, the company released a&nbsp;paper&nbsp;explaining the opportunities they are exploring in the metaverse.</p>



<p><strong>“There is a lot of client interest to learn more about the&nbsp;metaverse,”</strong> Christine Moy, JPMorgan’s head of crypto and the metaverse, said in an email. “We put together our white paper to help clients cut through the noise and highlight what the current reality is, and what needs to be built next in technology, commercial infrastructure, privacy/identity and workforce, in order to maximize the full potential of our lives in the metaverse.”</p>



<p>With the mainstream acceptance of things like non-fungible tokens (NFT), the past year has seen a breathless advance into the metaverse, fueled by integrated commerce applications. In January, electronics giant Samsung opened a version of its New York store&nbsp;in Decentraland and in November Barbados&nbsp;established a metaverse embassy, also in Decentraland.</p>



<p>JPMorgan begins its assessment of “metanomics” by pointing out that the average price of a parcel of virtual land doubled in the latter half of 2021, jumping from $6,000 in June to $12,000 by December across the four main Web 3 metaverse sites: Decentraland, The Sandbox, Somnium Space and Cryptovoxels.</p>



<p>“In time, the virtual real estate market could start seeing services much like in the physical world, including credit, mortgages and rental agreements,” said the JPMorgan report. It added that decentralized finance&nbsp;collateral management could well come into play, and that rather than traditional finance companies this could be done by decentralized autonomous organizations (DAO).</p>



<p>The JPMorgan report wasn’t all positive, however. In a section titled “Navigating hype vs. reality, “the report states,” despite much excitement about the possibilities of the Metaverse, in order to enable its full potential for engagement , community building, self – expression and commerce, key areas need to be further developed and matured, “pointing to flaws in the overall user experience, poor performance of avatars and difficulties with commercial infrastructure.</p>



<h4 id="a-major-role-in-the-metaverse"><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0)" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">A Major Role in The Metaverse</mark></h4>



<p>In the bank’s announcement paper, JPMorgan revealed that its planning to “play a major role in the metaverse”. &nbsp;The banking agency explained that it plans to help deal with issues that the crypto space has, mainly fraud. Essentially, the bank wishes to behind a centralied service in a decentralised environment.</p>



<p>The bank’s Metaverse push is inspired by the explosion of Metaverse real estate sales. With some&nbsp;fake properties selling for more than real house prices,&nbsp;the bank wants to get a slice of that profitable pie.</p>



<p>“This democratic ownership economy coupled with the possibility of interoperability, could unlock immense economic opportunities, whereby digital goods and services are no longer captive to a singular gaming platform or brand,” The bank writes.</p>



<p>Of course, Metaverse popularity is low, and the idea of digital services transcending single games into all games isn’t going to happen.</p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/jpmorgan-becomes-worlds-first-bank-in-the-metaverse/">JPMorgan becomes world&#8217;s first bank in the metaverse</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/jpmorgan-becomes-worlds-first-bank-in-the-metaverse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1857</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Coding Apps that you should Try at Least once in 2022</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-coding-apps-that-you-should-try-at-least-once-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-coding-apps-that-you-should-try-at-least-once-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pavithra Ravi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 02:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coding apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mimo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Programming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[programming hub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sololearn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top coding apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tynker]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>“Truth can only be found in one place: the code.” ―&#160;Robert C Considering how reliant the world has become on technology, one cannot ignore the fact that&#160;programming&#160;forms an integral part &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-coding-apps-that-you-should-try-at-least-once-in-2022/">Top Coding Apps that you should Try at Least once in 2022</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“Truth can only be found in one place: the code.”<br>                                                                         ―&nbsp;<strong>Robert C</strong></p></blockquote>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img src="https://static0.makeuseofimages.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/coding-apps.jpg" alt="coding apps"/></figure></div>



<p>Considering how reliant the world has become on technology, one cannot ignore the fact that&nbsp;programming&nbsp;forms an integral part of technology. Almost all the major companies across the globe rely on&nbsp;coding&nbsp;to accomplish their business goals.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="programming-hub"><a href="https://programminghub.io/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://programminghub.io/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Programming hub</a></h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><a href="https://programminghub.io/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img loading="lazy" src="https://th.bing.com/th/id/OIP.zy3VqZ5G9PtcE2zWd_kQuQHaHa?w=180&amp;h=180&amp;c=7&amp;r=0&amp;o=5&amp;dpr=1.5&amp;pid=1.7" alt="Programming hub" width="200" height="200"/></a></figure></div>



<p>       Right from Java, Python, C++ to Scala and Julia, <a href="http://programminghub.io" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="programminghub.io" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Programming Hub</a> has got you covered. An attractive feature about this coding application is that the lessons here are presented in the form of a story. You also have a set of quizzes to answer after each section.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="sololearn"><a href="https://www.sololearn.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.sololearn.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">SoloLearn</a></h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><a href="https://www.sololearn.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img loading="lazy" src="https://th.bing.com/th/id/OIP.KSMznDXlGSO8Bv6-oxqy9QHaHa?pid=ImgDet&amp;rs=1" alt="sololearn" width="200" height="200"/></a></figure></div>



<p>        <a href="https://www.sololearn.com/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.sololearn.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">SoloLearn </a>is a great programming application to go about. The app is such that the lessons can be tailored to your specific needs, preferences, and market trends. One can learn a wide range of languages including JavaScript, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Swift, Java, C++, PHP Ruby, etc.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="mimo"><a href="https://getmimo.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://getmimo.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Mimo</a></h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><a href="https://getmimo.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img loading="lazy" src="https://th.bing.com/th/id/OIP.Tr0ZitPdQkI_UyjHfLkgnAAAAA?w=173&amp;h=180&amp;c=7&amp;r=0&amp;o=5&amp;dpr=1.5&amp;pid=1.7" alt="Mimo" width="200" height="200"/></a></figure></div>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This&nbsp;coding application&nbsp;hosts a series of&nbsp;programming&nbsp;languages like Python, JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, SQL, Swift, Kotlin, C++, SQL, and PHP. Additionally, this application is simple and boasts a friendly interface.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="enki"><a href="https://www.enki.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.enki.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Enki</a></h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://www.enki.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://d1qb2nb5cznatu.cloudfront.net/startups/i/667561-d5acfddafc6bba6aaa31a95094bbfc59-medium_jpg.jpg?buster=1436988723" alt="Enki
"/></a></figure></div>



<p>     <a href="https://www.enki.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Enki </a>is quite similar to other coding applications such as SoloLearn. Enki offers a variety of coding courses including Python and JavaScript. Also, Enki boasts of having one of the most accessible and attractive interfaces I’ve seen.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="tynker"><a href="https://www.tynker.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.tynker.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Tynker</a></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="https://www.tynker.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://149455152.v2.pressablecdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/Tynker-1.jpg" alt=""/></a></figure>



<p>      <a href="https://www.tynker.com/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.tynker.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Tynker </a>has gained recognition as one of the most popular coding applications for kids. What keeps kids hooked to programming is the learning process that involves coding games, camps, challenges, and other learning activities.</p>



<h6 id="related-blog">Related blog</h6>



<p> <a href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/why-python/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/why-python/">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/why-python/</a></p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-coding-apps-that-you-should-try-at-least-once-in-2022/">Top Coding Apps that you should Try at Least once in 2022</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-coding-apps-that-you-should-try-at-least-once-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1928</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Check out the Dark Side of Phishing Attack</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yogesh K B]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[cyber Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybercrime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cybersecurity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pen testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[penetration testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[phishing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is Phishing? Phishing is an attack strategy that uses deception to solicit sensitive information or directly breach a system, typically in the form of an email. Although phishing is almost &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/">Check out the Dark Side of Phishing Attack</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 id="what-is-phishing"><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">What is Phishing?</mark></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://blog.malwarebytes.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/shutterstock_749866270-900x506.jpg" alt="Phishing "/></figure>



<p>Phishing is an attack strategy that uses deception to solicit sensitive information or directly breach a system, typically in the form of an email. Although phishing is almost as old as email, it has become increasingly more sophisticated, often evading spam filters and human detection.</p>



<h2 id="what-is-the-goal-of-phishing"><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">What is the <strong>Goal of Phishing?</strong></mark></h2>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Breaching a System</mark></strong></p>



<p>Some phish is used to get malicious code past the perimeter. Initial scrutiny is vital in this case because all it takes is a click and the malware can begin to download itself to your computer. Often, malware will lurk unsuspected in the system, either quietly collecting data or waiting to strike so the user may never realize that what they clicked was malicious. These emails contain either an attachment, a download, or a link to a website that will deliver a malware payload. This malware could be any number of things &#8211; crypto-mining malware, worms, ransomware, or other cyber threats.</p>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Gathering Sensitive Credentials</mark></strong></p>



<p>Phishing is also used as a means for gathering credentials, which can then be used for further attacks. This typically requires users to have to type in their personal information in some way, which is usually achieved by linking the target to a threat actor’s website. Users have more time to determine if the site is legitimate, so more work may go into making it look realistic, perhaps spoofing websites, using covert redirects, or ensuring the email appears as though it comes from a trustworthy source.</p>



<h2 id="what-are-the-different-types-of-phish"><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">What are the <strong>different types of Phish?</strong></mark></h2>



<p>The most familiar type of phish is also the most basic. These emails cast a wide net, and vary in terms of how realistic they are, but are aimed at a general audience to get clicks from careless or unaware employees. However, other, more specific types of phish are also used, including:</p>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Spear phishing</mark></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://academy.avast.com/hs-fs/hubfs/New_Avast_Academy/What_Is_Spear_Phishing_and_How_to_Avoid_It_Academy/Avast-Spear-Phishing.png?width=1320&amp;name=Avast-Spear-Phishing.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Spear phishing uses targeted attacks against a specific person or organization. A threat actor researches to learn personal information to tailor emails accordingly. For example, a phish could be created to look like an individual’s specific bank, or an organization may be phished with emails that appear to be from those working in human resources. Since spear phish is from familiar names or organizations and often looks more realistic, users are much more likely to open them.</p>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Whaling</mark></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://nordvpn.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/whaling-attack.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Whaling is an even more precise type of phish aimed at high-level targets, like C-level executives. While threat actors must again carefully research and craft an email that is not only tailor-made, whaling presents an additional challenge. Since such high-profile individuals are typically more selective about the emails they open, malicious actors put more thought into getting their attention in the emails they craft.</p>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Smashing</mark></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://twelvesec.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/Smishing.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Threat actors utilize every communication method, including short message services (SMS). Attackers send text messages or use messaging apps to solicit personal information or spread malicious links. Malicious links opened on a cell phone are particularly dangerous, since there typically isn’t antivirus software to protect these devices.</p>



<p><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Vishing</mark></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://indiaforensic.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/07/vishing.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Not all phish is in email form. People can receive automated or live calls requesting personal information that can be given in person or dialed into the keypad. Now that caller ID is universal, many vishing attacks also incorporate spoofing, in which a phone number from a local area code, or even a recognized company, appears to be calling. The most common vishing attacks include calls from banks, credit card companies, loan offers, car companies, or even charitable requests</p>



<h2 id="conclusion"><strong><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-red-color">Conclusion</mark></strong></h2>



<p>Phishing is considered one of the most effective attack vectors being used today. According to the Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report, 94 percent&nbsp;of malware deliveries are&nbsp;completed through a phishing email of some type. It is&nbsp;more critical than ever to learn what phishing is and avoid becoming the next victim.</p>



<p><strong>Reference: </strong></p>



<p><a href="https://www.coresecurity.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">https://www.coresecurity.com/</a></p>



<p><strong>Related blog: </strong></p>



<p><a href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/what-should-do-you-after-a-pen-test/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/what-should-do-you-after-a-pen-test/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/what-should-do-you-after-a-pen-test/</a></p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/">Check out the Dark Side of Phishing Attack</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/check-out-the-dark-side-of-phishing-attack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1914</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terrace Gardening! Tips and Steps</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/terrace-gardening-tips-and-steps/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/terrace-gardening-tips-and-steps/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[garden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terrace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terracegardening]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pollution has contaminated the air we breathe, the food we eat, and the water we drink. We can protect the environment as well as our bodies by planting plants&#8230;. It &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/terrace-gardening-tips-and-steps/">Terrace Gardening! Tips and Steps</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Pollution has contaminated the air we breathe, the food we eat, and the water we drink. We can protect the environment as well as our bodies by planting plants&#8230;. It may be a minor contribution to the environment, but it can assist us in leading a more fulfilling life. However, the vast majority of us live in apartments and buildings with no agricultural grounds or gardens in which to raise plants. You may solve this problem by creating a green space directly in your own house, on your terrace or balcony. Terraces receive plenty of sunlight, and gardening is calming and helps you connect with nature. This garden will also absorb carbon dioxide, reducing the heat in your home&#8217;s surroundings. Spend only a half-hour in the morning and a half-hour in the evening looking to your plants. You may grow beautiful trees, flowers, herbs, bushes, and even your own vegetables, all of which are pesticide-free and organic.</p>



<h2 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="here-tips-and-steps-for-terrace-gardening">Here, tips and steps for terrace gardening</h2>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="1-plant-the-layout">1.Plant the layout</h3>



<ul><li>You can create a terrace garden in one of two ways: you can cover the entire surface with soil to create a lawn, or you can use plant pots to grow plants in.</li><li>Because a terrace has fewer square feet than a typical garden, it is vital to arrange the space usage correctly.</li><li>Look for regions that are shaded, as well as areas that receive sunlight for the most of the day. If you&#8217;re going to have a sitting area on the terrace, decide where it will go.</li><li>Plants need to be sheltered from direct sunshine in the summer, and you may do so by creating a shade. Choose a location for this.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="2-choose-your-plants">2. Choose your plants</h3>



<ul><li>To grow, start with something small.</li><li>If you want to cultivate veggies, start with those that grow quickly and take little effort, such as coriander, fenugreek, chilli, capsicum, and so on.</li><li>Fibre-rooted plants are generally preferred.</li><li>If your terrace has pillars, you can use them to support climbers such as bottle gourds and cucumbers.</li><li>Begin with jasmine, periwinkle, lavender, rosemary, primrose, and other terrace gardening plants.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="3-water-resistance">3. Water-resistance</h3>



<ul><li>One crucial step is to make the terrace&#8217;s flooring water-proof / water-resistant so that watering plants does not cause harm to the building.</li><li>It&#8217;s a simple technique with a variety of water-proofing materials from which to choose.</li><li>An insulation layer must be placed over the waterproofing layer to protect it.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="4-soil-preparation">4. Soil preparation</h3>



<ul><li>The soil should be chosen based on the plants you want to grow. Basically, create a highly rich soil with adequate moisture and minerals.</li><li>Check the pH of the soil and add some compost, vermicompost, or other organic matter to the mix.</li><li>It&#8217;s available in any local nursery or on the internet.</li><li>Alternatively, you can purchase the components, make your own compost (ideally household compost), and mix the soil.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="5-containers-or-pots-for-plants">5. Containers or pots for plants</h3>



<ul><li>For your garden, you can utilise a variety of pots. To decorate the garden, use earthen pots, cement pots, grow bags, or hanging pots in a variety of forms, sizes, and colours.</li><li>You may also grow plants in old paint boxes, wooden crates, broken buckets, cooking utensils, and coconut shells.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="6-seeds">6. Seeds</h3>



<ul><li>Either purchase seeds or use the seeds from the vegetables you purchase. Examine the characteristics of the plants you intend to develop.</li></ul>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="7-additional-needs-and-watering">7. Additional needs and watering</h3>



<ul><li>Plants should be watered on a regular basis (according to the season: twice a day in summer, once a day in winter, after 2-3days in rainy season). For a fast and healthy plant growth, apply insecticides and fertilisers.</li><li>Use kitchen trash, cow manure, and other organic fertilisers if you want 100 percent organic growth.</li><li>A terrace garden is simple to start. You must keep it in good condition by watering it properly, inspecting it for pests, and fertilising it. Simply put aside one hour per day to create a stunning terrace garden for yourself.</li></ul>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/terrace-gardening-tips-and-steps/">Terrace Gardening! Tips and Steps</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/terrace-gardening-tips-and-steps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1859</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Easy and Mouth-Watering Dishes you should try at Home!</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/5-easy-and-mouth-watering-dishes-you-should-try-at-home/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/5-easy-and-mouth-watering-dishes-you-should-try-at-home/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Clara Queeni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5 easy dishes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dishes you should try at home]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Easy and mouth-watering dishes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tastey food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How yummy the title is even! Right ? Save your extra time by looking at our 8 easy andscrumptious food dishes that you should try at home! Serve your loved &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/5-easy-and-mouth-watering-dishes-you-should-try-at-home/">5 Easy and Mouth-Watering Dishes you should try at Home!</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/64698744.cms" alt="" width="485" height="364"/></figure></div>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><strong><em>How yummy the title is even! Right ? Save your extra time by looking at our 8 easy and<br>scrumptious food dishes that you should try at home! Serve your loved ones and your kids to<br>delight their day. Come on, let&#8217;s get into our blog..</em></strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-left has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="chocolate-mug-cake">Chocolate mug cake</h3>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://cf-images.eu-west-1.prod.boltdns.net/v1/static/1786863135/95056ed8-032a-4a8a-acf5-c22ad243335b/40b9e7a1-17ae-4086-9559-a5910d61eed8/640x360/match/image.jpg" alt="" width="567" height="319"/><figcaption><em>A mug cake is a great alternative to nip that craving in the bud! Let’s see the easiest<br>way to make it…</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<h4 id="ingredients"><strong>Ingredients</strong></h4>



<p class="has-text-align-left">● 4 tablespoons flour<br>● 3 tablespoons sugar<br>● 2 tablespoons cocoa powder<br>● ½ teaspoon baking powder<br>● 3 tablespoons milk<br>● 1 tablespoon oil, vegetable or canola<br>● 1 teaspoon vanilla extract<br>● 1 tablespoon chocolate hazelnut spread, plus more for topping<br>● Powdered sugar for topping, this is completely optional</p>



<h4 id="preparation"><strong>Preparation</strong></h4>



<p>The best part is preparing all these yummy ingredients together!<br>● Mix all the ingredients together , except the chocolate hazelnut spread<br>● Once combined, spoon the chocolate hazelnut spread on top of the batter.<br>● Microwave on high for 90 seconds to 2 minutes<br>● Top with additional chocolate hazelnut spread and powdered sugar (optional)<br>● You can add vanilla ice cream on top too! Enjoy and serve!</p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-left has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="sizzling-chilli-oil-maggi">Sizzling chilli oil Maggi</h2>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i0.wp.com/thestrongtraveller.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/masala-maggi.jpg?resize=640%2C360&amp;ssl=1" alt="" width="556" height="313"/><figcaption><em>Who hasn&#8217;t tasted the heavenly feeling of a hot plate of Maggi when stricken with<br>hunger? That’s the best feeling right ?! Alright, adding more taste to it, have you ever<br>tried sizzling chilli Maggi? Then let’s try since the mentioned spices have been roasted<br>to perfection, providing a distinct aroma and colour to your MAGGI noodles.</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<h4 id="ingredients-1"><strong>Ingredients</strong></h4>



<p>● Olive/refined/sesame oil<br>● 1 tbsp spring onion<br>● 2 gloves garlic<br>● ½ sugar ,Ginger ¼ tbsp<br>● 1 tbsp coriander leaves<br>● 1 tbsp red chilli flakes<br>● ½ tbsp Kashmiri red chilli powder(for colour)<br>● 2 tbsp sesame seeds<br>● Maggi masala<br>● Vinegar, Dark soy sauce</p>



<h4 id="preparation-1"><strong>Preparation</strong></h4>



<p>● In a Bowl, take 2 Cloves Garlic Pods finely chopped , 2 Tsp sesame seeds,1 tbsp<br>spring onion, 1 tsp red chilly flakes,1/2 tsp kashmiri red chilly powder for colour<br>,1/2 tsp sugar, Ginger 1/4 TSP, Coriander Leaves 1 TSP.<br>● Heat 1.5-2 tbsp oil ( sesame / olive / refined )and pour hot oil on this ( specially<br>on top of garlic and mix well.<br>● Add 2 TSP Dark Soy sauce, 1/2 tsp Vinegar and Maggi masala mix ( the packet<br>that comes along) and mix well<br>● Boil Maggi in around 2.5-3 cups water, don&#8217;t put less water or else your maggi<br>will be sticky. Don&#8217;t over boil<br>● Add to the bowl…mix…garnish with some sesame seeds …Enjoy!</p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-left has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="honey-chilli-potato">Honey chilli potato</h2>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1PgbAyRPbQs/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="" width="566" height="318"/><figcaption><em>Potatoes are very much loved as a snack for younger generations so, If you love honey<br>chilli potato , then you must try this recipe!</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<h4 id="ingredients-2"><strong>Ingredients</strong></h4>



<p>● Garlic, sesame seeds<br>● Onion, Capsicum<br>● Green chilly<br>● Soy sauce<br>● Vinegar<br>● Ketchup<br>● Red Chilli sauce<br>● Pepper<br>● Honey<br>● Corn flour paste<br>● Fried potatoes</p>



<h4 id="preparation-2"><strong>Preparation</strong></h4>



<p>● In a pan, add all the ingredients mentioned above and stir it well<br>● After frying the potatoes ( the shape can be of your choice ,French fries the better)<br>● Adding the potatoes and mix all well<br>● Serve with sprinkled spring onions!</p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-left has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="crispy-cheese-balls">Crispy Cheese balls</h2>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.foodieist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/dzdf-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="567" height="313"/><figcaption><em>Our love for cheese is a constantly flourishing affair that never ends!</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<h4 id="ingredients-3"><strong>Ingredients</strong></h4>



<p>● Boiled potato<br>● Cheese<br>● Ginger<br>● Green chilly<br>● Salt<br>● Chilly flakes<br>● 4 tbsp All purpose flour<br>● 2 tbsp corn flour</p>



<h4 id="preparation-3"><strong>Preparation</strong></h4>



<p>● First, take a bowl and add boiled potatoes,few ginger and green chilly finely<br>grinded , add lots of cheese<br>● Add some mixed of chilli flakes and all purpose flour for binding<br>● Don’t forget to add some salt<br>● Combine everything well and shape them into small balls<br>● Add a chunk of cheese in every ball you make to add some extra cheesy flavour<br>and dip it in corn flour batter<br>● After frying in oil, our cheesy and crunchy cheese balls are ready to serve! Serve<br>with mayo dip and enjoy !</p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-left has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="red-sauce-pasta">Red sauce pasta</h2>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.homestratosphere.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Pasta-with-tomato-sauce-5-29-6-min.jpg" alt="" width="535" height="357"/><figcaption><em>Over time, because of pasta&#8217;s affordability, shelf life, and versatility, it became firmly<br>rooted in Italian culture. Let’s see if you like our red sauce pasta recipe!</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<h4 id="ingredients-4"><strong>Ingredients</strong></h4>



<p>● Olive oil<br>● Garlic<br>● Onions<br>● Veggies<br>● Tomato paste<br>● Mixed herbs<br>● Chilli flakes<br>● Salt, Sugar<br>● Ketchup<br>● Half boiled pasta</p>



<h4 id="preparation-4"><strong>Preparation</strong></h4>



<p>● In a pan with hot olive oil add garlic ,give it a quick mix<br>● Add onions and saute it ,add veggies ( of your choice)<br>● Next , add tomato paste and cook it for 5 mins<br>● Mix the herbs and chilli flakes . Add salt and sugar with ketchup.<br>● Finally add the boiled pasta to the pan, mix all and now it’s ready !!</p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/5-easy-and-mouth-watering-dishes-you-should-try-at-home/">5 Easy and Mouth-Watering Dishes you should try at Home!</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/5-easy-and-mouth-watering-dishes-you-should-try-at-home/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1838</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Unique Places To Visit In India</title>
		<link>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/10-unique-places-to-visit-in-india/</link>
					<comments>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/10-unique-places-to-visit-in-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nithish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 03:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[10 places to visit in india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Places to visit in india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unique places in india]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blogs.techsnapie.com/?p=1802</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>India has certain unique places that are known for their quirky and interesting culture. So adventure seekers out there, visit these unique places in India and quench your thirst for &#8230; </p>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/10-unique-places-to-visit-in-india/">10 Unique Places To Visit In India</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>India has certain unique places that are known for their quirky and interesting culture. So adventure seekers out there, visit these unique places in India and quench your thirst for adventure.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="1-lamayuru">1. Lamayuru</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/65193856.cms" alt=" Lamayuru"/></figure>



<p><br>It’s a small village in Ladakh, but an ideal place to take a break from the journey from Kargil to Leh. Home of one of the oldest monasteries in Ladakh, legends believe that this place was once a lake that dried up. Remains on top of the Leh tourism charts, this tiny village has more to offer than it meets your eyes. Lamayuru is popular for its ‘lunar’ landscape and monastery. Interestingly, this quaint little village is promoted as ‘moonscape’ for tourists; the reason being its incredible yet odd geographical formations</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="2-betaab-valley">2. Betaab Valley</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.tourmyindia.com/states/jammu-kashmir/image/betaab-valley-pahalgam2.jpg" alt="Betaab Valley"/></figure>



<p><br>Betaab Valley was originally known as Hagan Valley or Hagoon, but came to be known by its present name &amp; became extremely famous after the movie Betaab, which was shot here. It is located almost 15 kilometers from Pahalgam in the Anantnag district of Jammu and Kashmir. What makes the valley a top tourist attraction in Jammu &amp; Kashmir is its lush meadows, mountains and dense vegetation, which offers lovely opportunities for sightseeing &amp; is a photographer’s delight.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="3-jaisalmer">3. Jaisalmer</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/f/ff/View_from_Jaisalmer_fort.jpg/1200px-View_from_Jaisalmer_fort.jpg" alt=" Jaisalmer"/></figure>



<p><br>Jaisalmer is a former medieval trading center and a princely state in the western Indian state of Rajasthan, in the heart of the Thar Desert. Known as the &#8220;Golden City,&#8221; it&#8217;s distinguished by its yellow sandstone architecture. Dominating the skyline is Jaisalmer Fort, a sprawling hilltop citadel buttressed by 99 bastions. Behind its massive walls stand the ornate Maharaja&#8217;s Palace and intricately carved Jain temples.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="4-puga-valley">4. Puga Valley</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://thumbs.dreamstime.com/b/ladakh-india-aug-grassland-hemis-shukpachan-village-sham-valley-jammu-kashmir-188501512.jpg" alt="unique places" width="701" height="468"/></figure>



<p><br>Puga Valley in the Ladakh region of Jammu &amp; Kashmir was one of the areas which showed significant potential for geothermal energy. Puga lies in the south-eastern part of Ladakh and forms a part of the Himalayan geothermal belt. … A shallow excavation to look for a source for geothermal energy in Ladakh.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="5-punaluʻu-beach">5. Punaluʻu Beach</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.lovebigisland.com/wp-content/uploads/punaluu-black-sand-beach.jpg" alt="Punaluʻu Beach "/></figure>



<p><br>Punaluʻu Beach is a beach between Pāhala and Nāʻālehu on the Big Island of the U.S. state of Hawaii. The beach has black sand made of basalt and created by lava flowing into the ocean which explodes as it reaches the ocean and cools. This volcanic activity is in the Hawaiʻi Volcanoes National Park.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="6-tso-kar">6. Tso Kar</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.tourmyindia.com/states/ladakh/imagess/tso-kar-lake-ladakh3.jpg" alt="Tsho kar"/></figure>



<p><br>The Tso Kar or Tsho kar is a fluctuating salt lake known for its size and depth situated in the Rupshu Plateau and valley in the southern part of Ladakh in India. It is also recognized as India’s 42nd Ramsar site.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="7-gulmarg">7. Gulmarg</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://d2rdhxfof4qmbb.cloudfront.net/wp-content/uploads/20190226111609/iStock-925211470.jpg" alt="gulmarg"/></figure>



<p><br>Gulmarg, known as Gulmarg in Kashmiri, is a town, hill station, popular skiing destination, and notified area committee in the Baramulla district of Jammu and Kashmir, India. It is located at a distance of 31 km from Baramulla and 49 km from Srinagar.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="8-cabo-de-rama">8. Cabo de Rama</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://adventurebuddha.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Cabo-De-Rama-Beach-Goa-1280x720.jpg" alt="Cabo de Rama"/></figure>



<p><br>Visiting the Cabo de Rama fort will be like a journey back in time. You’ll witness the fort is mostly in ruins, yet it’s a historical marvel due to its magnificent architecture. Cabo de Rama is one of the best shots to know about Hindu Mythology, and Hindu as well as Portuguese rule – everything at a single stop.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="9-alappuzha">9. Alappuzha</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://img.onmanorama.com/content/dam/mm/en/travel/travel-news/images/2018/5/21/houseboat-alappuzha.jpg" alt="alappuzha"/></figure>



<p><br>Alappuzha is a city on the Laccadive Sea in the southern Indian state of Kerala. It’s best known for houseboat cruises along the rustic Kerala backwaters, a network of tranquil canals and lagoons. Alappuzha Beach is the site of the 19th-century Alappuzha Lighthouse. The city’s Mullakkal Temple features a traditional design. Punnamada Lake’s snake boat races are a well-known annual event.</p>



<h3 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color" id="10-valley-of-flowers">10. Valley of Flowers</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://indiahikes.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Valley-Of-Flowers_VOF_Rupesh-Thakare-ValleyOfFlowers-1024x683.jpg" alt="Valley of flower" width="698" height="465"/></figure>



<p><br>They were right when they said &#8216;beauty can be a cruel mistress. The Valley of Flowers in Uttarakhand is so beautiful that it attracts a lot of tourists, and that is the biggest threat to the region. There is a thin line between an ideal trekking destination and a burgeoning tourist hub and we seem to have crossed that when it comes to Valley of Flower.</p>



<h2 class="has-vivid-red-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size" id="related-blogs">Related blogs:</h2>



<ul><li> <a href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/top-5-attracting-tourist-destination-in-india-2022/"> Top 5 Attracting Tourist Destination in India 2022</a></li></ul>
<p>&lt;p&gt;The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com/10-unique-places-to-visit-in-india/">10 Unique Places To Visit In India</a> first appeared on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blogs.techsnapie.com">Techsnapie Magazines</a>.&lt;/p&gt;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blogs.techsnapie.com/10-unique-places-to-visit-in-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1802</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
